so when we first met Kevin was quiet
kind of shy then one night at a bar we
ended up using the urinals next to each
other suddenly changed
Kevin's clients have told me he's making
sales calls from the bathroom when I
asked him why he says it's because he's
multitasking
I heard he's even recording a podcast in
there welcome back to shooting the pits
podcast today we have a very special
surprise guest row I never see him
anymore without his Camelback and he's
constantly popping diuretics the kid's
gonna wear out his bladder with all that
soda if he doesn't stop he won't be
pissing in a urinal he'll be pissing in
an adult diaper whoa guys
there's no not here you haveno what none
of us read books nobody does Kevin we're
here to talk about your obsession with
urinal chitchat oh you guys want to talk
mind if I just take a piss well no this
is an intervention or talking at the
urinal you know small talk that's
annoying enough but you're always trying
to get all deep like asking questions
about my mom scout oh how is she doing
with those anti inflammatories by the
way sorry no no you're good okay I'm
doing
[Music]
drink a lot of cobble that was
disgusting the way it smelled I know
right no you obviously we can all smell
that he has coffee piss you just started
the conversation because you wanted to I
was just being friendly you guys are all
crazy us you installed a 40 inch flat
screen with all access cable just so you
could trick guys in here and then talk
to them about sports who doesn't want to
talk about baseball when they're pissing
named one baseball player
Buster Scruggs what see you don't know
anything about sports you just use it as
a talking point
Nice Kicks you ball dude come on yeah
okay I didn't have to talk to him I was
just curious all right why do you so
desperately need to talk in here it's
just guys being guys getting intimate
you know your nose break barriers
there's the most vulnerable and honest
when you're taking a piss Kevin I'm
going to meet you halfway
you can hold your dick at work when
you're talking other employees do this
Kevin we all love you but you have a
problem you replace the toilet in your
apartment with a urinal that's just more
convenient wit where do you I don't
I'm on an all liquid diet oh god you are
destroying your body man Kevin you sick
I'm not sick listen if it makes you all
happy I'll just stop I'll stop talking
to people at the urinal and what about
outside the urinal are you gonna be able
to open up to people without your
porcelain security blanket for sure so
you're gonna stop talking at a urinal
cold turkey yes
[Music]
oh come on
no dude you know you're gonna use the
end of urine oh right so I'll find out
to talk to you then check that hold on
your shoes
those nights
you know I recently been calling it
caramel and instead of caramel I used to
call it caramel but I definitely think
it's care about now what do you think
still there hello
[Music]